Guide to the Ron Kolm Papers, 1970-2016 MSS.079
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VIII: Original Art
  - Appearances # 17: "Suburban Ambush" issue. Original art Works by: Ken Brown, Jorga Cardin, Ken Tisa, & other unsigned. 8 pieces total, undated (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - Big Fish Magazine-- "No Words" Issue-- Original Art. Unsigned, undated (Box 10, Folder 39)
  - Brown, Ken -- 2 "Wrap City Sheets", undated (Box 10, Folder 40)
  - Cardin, Jorga --9 works, 2 of them oversized, undated (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - CAREN, Original for Poetry Reading announcement on an aerogramme + 1 copy, undated (Box 10, Folder 42)
  - Deyab, Larry-- 6 cards and one "work on paper", undated (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - Drooker, Eric-- 4 works, undated (Box 10, Folder 44)
  - Hell is where everything faces the ground. Unsigned. #NAME?, undated (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - Hutchinson, Bruce-- 12 black and white works on cardstock + accompanying envelope, undated (Box 10, Folder 46)
  - Isaac, Jeffrey--3 originals for poetry reading announcements, undated (Box 10, Folder 47)
  - Kolm, Ron (Box 10, Folder 48)
  - Kostabi, Mark --1 original art for a poetry reading announcement for reading by Richard Bandanza, Ron Kolm, & Carmelita Tropicana at the St. Mark's Poetry Project "March 17th" no year cited, undated (Box 10, Folder 49)
  - Madore, Michael -- 1 original art for a poetry reading announcement at "Back Fence" by Samuel Menashe, Michael LaBombarda, and Thomas McGonigle, undated (Box 10, Folder 50)
  - Moisan, Jim -- 2 originals of reading announcement for Low Tech Press, undated (Box 10, Folder 51)
  - Randall, Michael --33 drawings, undated (Box 10, Folder 52)
  - Raveson, Art--4 originals for poetry reading announcements, undated (Box 10, Folder 53)
  - Spiegelman, Art -- 1 limited black and white print with accompanying letter from Random House, Inc, undated (Box 10, Folder 54)
  - Spiegelman, Art-1 chromolithograph from "The Wild Party" Signed and Framed, undated (Box 1, Folder 18A)
  - Stevenson, Patrick -- 39 works. Including black & white drawings, 1 color work, for calendars, reading announcements, etc, undated (Box 10, Folder 55)
  - Witz, Bob -- 1 black and white drawing, possibly of Allen Ginsberg, with blue pen marks over face, undated (Box 10, Folder 56)
  - Zummer, Thomas -- Zummer file #1 Color and black and white works. 87 pages, undated (Box 10, Folder 57)
  - Zummer, Thomas -- Zummer file #2 94 pages, including the series: "Tales Of Drama and Inconvenience," "Brain Dead Dog," "Tales From Zummerville", undated (Box 10, Folder 58)
  - Zummer, Thomas -- Zummer file # 3 5 works on paper, in color 1 work on paper, black and white, 1 color card with the words "you're right it's the wise men and they've got them pointed right at us", undated (Box 10, Folder 59)
  - Zummer, Thomas -- Zummer #4 Art (Box 10, Folder 60)
- Series IX: Ephemera
  This series contains ephemeral objects, and includes Keith Haring pins, matchbook poems, pencil poems, stamp art, sticker art, sticker poems, and a ping pong ball announcement from CBGB's, amongst other like items.
  - R. Crumb Trading Cards, undated (Box 11)
  - Artkards 1992 Series (Box 11)
  - Heroes of the Blues Cards, undated (Box 11)
  - Crackpots & Visionaries Vol. 2 Cards, David Sandlin, artist, undated (Box 11)
  - Early Jazz Greats Cards, undated (Box 11)
  - RAW buttons (in a round, plastic container), undated (Box 11)
  - 3 Pencils by Beth Lapides. (Actual pencils.), undated (Box 11)
  - 6 Matchbooks (w. poem by Ron Kolm), undated (Box 11)
  - 1 button by William Anthony, undated (Box 11)
  - 1 matchbook called SUN/NIGHT w. poem by James Pelletier, undated (Box 11)
  - 1 Charles Bukowski/Black Sparrow button, undated (Box 11)
  - 1 button from Coalition To Stop U.S. Intervention In The Middle East, undated (Box 11)
  - WFMU by Kaz, undated (Box 11)
  - The Product Is You Sticker, with text by William Burroughs Ragged Edge Press, undated (Box 11)
  - Art Spiegelman Cards, undated (Box 10, Folder 61)
  - Janet Restino Cards, undated (Box 10, Folder 62)
  - RAW #1 Cards, undated (Box 10, Folder 63)
  - Miscellaneous Printed Ephemera (Business Cards, Bookmarks, etc.), undated (Box 10, Folder 64)
- Series X: Low Tech Press
  This series consists of production Files for Low Tech Press, Ron Kolm's small press.
  - The Catering Hall, undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Famous French Poets, undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Girlie Pictures (oversized), undated (Box 1, Folder 2A)
  - Low Tech, undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Low Tech Manual, undated (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Low Tech Press, undated (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Monkey by Max Blagg (oversized), undated (Box 1, Folder 5A)
  - Suburban Ambush, undated (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Welcome To The Barbecue, undated (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Welcome To The Barbecue, undated (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Welcome To The Barbecue--2nd Edition Corrections, undated (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Welcome To The Barbecue--3rd Edition--4th Edition, undated (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Welcome To The Barbecue--5th Edition, undated (Box 12, Folder 11)
  - Miscellaneous Receipts & Tax Records, undated (Box 12, Folder 12)
  - Zummer, Tom--"Make Love Not War" w. Ron Kolm (oversized), undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Series XI: Posters
  This series contains posters Kolm collected from the downtown scene. Included are posters for the Sex Pistols as well as posters for many downtown books, such as Raw magazine, and a variety of signed prints by downtown artists.
  - Art: Bill Anthony, undated (Folder 3 Left)
  - Art: David Sandlin, undated (Folder 20)
  - Galleries & Artists, undated (Folder 2 Left)
  - Literature. Miscellaneous, undated (Folder 5 Left)
  - Magazines, Readings; Mickey Mao by Ken Brown, undated (Folder 1 Left)
  - RAW Magazine, undated (Folder 7 Left)
  - Unbearables, undated (Folder 21)
  - Performances, undated (Box Shared Fales 086, Folder 7)
  - St. Mark's Poetry Project, undated (Box Shared Fales 086, Folder 4)
  - Poodle with a Mohawk, undated (Folder 13 Right)
  - Sex Pistols "Fuck Forever" (1986), undated (Folder 18)
- Series XII: Catalogs
  This series consists of catalogues from small and independent presses, and consortia who published downtown works.
  - Amok Press, undated (Box 12, Folder 13)
  - Anti Catalog, undated (Box 12, Folder 14)
  - Art Market Catalogue, undated (Box 12, Folder 15)
  - Assembling Press Publications, undated (Box 12, Folder 16)
  - Autonomedia, undated (Box 12, Folder 17)
  - Black Ice Books, undated (Box 12, Folder 18)
  - Black Sparrow Press, undated (Box 12, Folder 19)
  - Blast Books, undated (Box 12, Folder 20)
  - City Lights Publishers, undated (Box 12, Folder 21)
  - Dalkey Archives Press, undated (Box 12, Folder 22)
  - Burning Deck Books, undated (Box 12, Folder 23)
  - Four Walls/Eight Windows, undated (Box 12, Folder 24)
  - Garden Street Press, undated (Box 12, Folder 25)
  - Generations Unlimited, undated (Box 12, Folder 26)
  - Giorno Poetry Systems, undated (Box 12, Folder 27)
  - Granary Books, undated (Box 12, Folder 28)
  - Hanging Loose Press, undated (Box 12, Folder 29)
  - Hanuman Books, undated (Box 12, Folder 30)
  - High Risk/Serpent's Tail Books, undated (Box 12, Folder 31)
  - Jargon Society, undated (Box 12, Folder 32)
  - Kitchen Sink, undated (Box 12, Folder 33)
  - New York Small Press Association, undated (Box 12, Folder 34)
  - Photography In New York, undated (Box 12, Folder 35)
  - Printed Matter, Inc (1 of 2), undated (Box 12, Folder 36)
  - Printed Matter (2 of 2) (Box 12, Folder 37)
  - RAW, undated (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Red Dust, undated (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Riverside Writers Group, undated (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - Seven Stories Press, undated (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Small Press Distribution, undated (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - Tanam Press, undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Teachers & Writers Collaborative, undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Tellus, undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Thin Air Video, undated (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - Weighed Anchor Press, undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - WFMU "Curiosities Catalogs", undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Series XIV: Periodicals
  This series contains periodicals important to, featuring or produced by members of the downtown scene.
  - Benderson, Bruce "Goodbye Sleaze, Hello Disneyland," Cups magazine, #73, p. 9, undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - Cantsin, Monty, interview. The Neoist Conspiracy. Ipso Facto Magazine, # 4 Spring 1988., pp. 22-25 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - Cherches, Peter "Lift your right arm, she said." From Bagatelles. High Times magazine, March, 1982., p. 10 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - Cherches, Peter. Tales Of Ordinary Madness. Lightworks magazine, Number 18, Winter 1986-87. pp. 4 -- 10, 1986-1987 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - Davies, Bevan -- "Photographs" Genesis: Grasp, Vol. 1, #2. 1969. pp. 16 - 21 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - Eidus, Janice -- "Nautilus" Spec. magazine. n.d. pp. 50-53, undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - Eidus, Janice -- Interview, Cups magazine, p. 28, undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - Hardin, Rob -- 2 poems, Java Journal, Vol. 1, #8, November 1994. p. 10 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Haring, Keith -- Review of Haring's Journals, Rain Taxi magazine, p47, undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Holland, Barbara -- The Grendhal Poetry Review, #1., 1986. Six poems (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Kolm, Ron -- Low Tech Press quote. Writer's Digest magazine. Jun-84. p. 46, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Kolm, Ron -- Review of "Welcome To The Barbecue" Contact II, Summer 1982. p. 5 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Kolm, Ron -- "Suburban Ambush" (poem)., The Peabody Review #2, 1990. p. 19 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Kolm, Ron -- "Suburban Ambush" (poem), Heat #15, June 1985. Thirdm unnumbered page (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - Kolm, Ron -- Photo of Ron Kolm, High Times magazine, July 1981. p. 67 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - Kolm, Ron -- "Suburban Ambush" (poem) International Poetry Review, #2 October 1986. Unnumbered pages (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Kolm, Ron -- "Suburban Ambush" (poem) Sheep magazine. Feb-84. p. 62, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Kolm, Ron -- 2 poems. Arulo magazine. Volume #21, December 1982. pp. 14, 52 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Kolm, Ron -- "Self Help" text. Image: David Sandlin., Chemical Imbalance magazine, Vol. 2 #1, 1989. p. 100. Record included w. magazine (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - Kolm, Ron -- The Poetry Project Newsletter, #92. Oct-82. Ad for Low Tech Press, inside back cover, 1982 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - Kostabi, Mark -- 2 drawings. Rio magazine. Fall 1987. Unnumbered pages (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - Kostelanetz, Richard -- "Why Audio Drama Now?" Theater X magazine, 1986. p. 9 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - LaBombarda, Michael -- 2 poems, Samisdat magazine, Vol. IV, #4, Summer 1975. pp. 17, 18 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - LaBombarda, Michael -- "Poets Don't Lose Gunfights With The Moon" (poem) Source magazine, Vol. 2, #1, 1977. p. 11 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - McGrath, Patrick -- "Enter The Strange Realm Of Patrick McGrath," by Sean Abbott, "Mad Love In The Garden" by Patrick McGrath, p. 2l At Random, magazine. Random House, Inc. Winter, 1997 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Plantenga, Bart -- "Confessions Of A Beer Mystic", Big Dick Review, Volume 0, #1, Spring 1989. p. 1 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Plantenga, Bart -- "soon" (poem) Police Beat magazine #1, Spring, 1980. pp. 60-6l (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Plantenga, Bart -- "Melon Rinds We Have Eaten" (poem), Generation magazine, Volume XXVI, #1, 1975 (Box 14, Folder 28)
  - Plantenga, Bart -- "Paris Scratch" Prose. Joe Soap's Canoe magazine, 1992. unnumbered pages (Box 14, Folder 29)
  - Plantenga, Bart -- "Rhomboyd" The Nice Review, p. 14. Pages upside down, undated (Box 14, Folder 30)
  - Plantenga, Bart -- 9 works. Carsick magazine. 1977, pp. 3, 4, 7, 8, 15, 17, 23, 27, 34, 38 (Box 14, Folder 31)
  - Plantenga, Bart -- 6 works, The Art Of Darkness Magazine, 1978? (Box 14, Folder 32)
  - Plantenga, Bart -- "knew the tropic", Roadwerk magazine, #IV, 1984 (Box 14, Folder 33)
  - Plantenga, Bart -- "Really living: Adventures In Truth II" Yellow Silk magazine, #13, Winter 1984, p. 19 (Box 14, Folder 34)
  - Plantenga, Bart -- "Fellow De Se", Sandbox magazine #3, 1995. p. 14 (Box 14, Folder 35)
  - Plantenga, Bart -- Review of "Wiggling Wishbone" by Bart Plantenga. Paramour magazine, Vol. 2, #3 p. 26, undated (Box 14, Folder 36)
  - Sandlin, David -- "Sinland" Art? magazine, 1996, pp. 30-35 (Box 14, Folder 37)
  - Schiffrin, Anya -- "Panorama Literaria U.S.A" Ajoblanco magazine, 1987. pp. 90-91 (Box 14, Folder 38)
  - Schiffrin, Anya -- "Los Yuppies Asaltan El East Village" Ajoblanco magazine, 1988, pp. 56 -- 63 (Box 14, Folder 39)
  - Siegle, Robert -- Ad for "Suburban Ambush" anthology by Ron Kolm & Robert Siegle. Granta magazine #28, 1989 (Box 14, Folder 40)
  - Sirowitz, Hal -- 2 poems, Realities #3, broadside, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 41)
  - Sirowitz, Hal, "A Bullet Doesn't Stop At Flesh" Lusty Mover magazine, January 93, p. 12, 1993 (Box 14, Folder 42)
  - Sirowitz, Hal -- "These Are My Parents And This Is My Girl", (prose) Croton Review, magazine, 1985, pp. 49 - 51 (Box 14, Folder 43)
  - Sirowitz, Hal -- "Bumping Into An Ex- Lover," Lucky Star magazine, vol. 2, #3, October 1985, p. 11 (Box 14, Folder 44)
  - Sirowitz, Hal -- 19 poems, Newsletter Inago, July 1986 (Box 14, Folder 45)
  - Sirowitz, Hal -- "Submerging" attached to Bogg 53. Broadside. or ad, undated (Box 14, Folder 46)
  - Sirowitz, Hal -- "Pay Me A Visit", Without Halos magazine, Vol. 3, 1985. p. 4 (Box 14, Folder 47)
  - Sirowitz, Hal -- 2 poems, The Bare Foot Review, vol. 2, #1, 1989. pp. 15,16 (Box 14, Folder 48)
  - Sirowitz, Hal -- Announcement for "Girlie Pictures", Hanging Loose magazine, #43, Winter 1982-1983. p. 36 (Box 14, Folder 49)
  - Sirowitz, Hal -- "Designing Women's Clothes," Abraxas magazine 27/28. p. 43. Review of "Girlie Pictures" p. 59, undated (Box 14, Folder 50)
  - Sirowitz, Hal -- "Beginnings Are Important to Me," fiction, Writ magazine, #17, 1985 (Box 14, Folder 51)
  - Sirowitz, Hal -- "Death Gift" High Times magazine, January 1983. p. 9 (Box 14, Folder 52)
  - Sirowitz, Hal -- 2 poems. Wu Wei magazine, #8, unnumbered pages. n.d, undated (Box 14, Folder 53)
  - Sirowitz, Hal -- "The Sitting Dance," Poetry Motel magazine, #5, 1985, p.12 (Box 14, Folder 54)
  - Sirowitz, Hal --"She Got Paint All Over Her Robe," Greens magazine, p. 40, undated (Box 14, Folder 55)
  - Sirowitz, Hal -- "A Strange Man Was Breathing On My Phone," Folio magazine, Spring 1985, p. 9 (Box 14, Folder 56)
  - Sirowitz, Hal -- "Money, Money" Sonoma Mandala magazine Vol. 12. 1985 pp.64-65 (Box 14, Folder 57)
  - Sparrow -- "Talk Of The Town" Machete magazine, #1, 1994, p. 38 (Box 14, Folder 58)
  - Spiegelman, Art -- "The Wild Party", drawings, The New Yorker magazine, June/July 1994, pp. 155-163 (Box 14, Folder 59)
  - Sukenick, Ronald -- "The Underground Exposed", Cups magazine, June 1996. pp. 14-Dec (Box 14, Folder 60)
  - Tillman, Lynne -- Interview. Cups magazine, #69 p. 24. Interview by Rob Hardin, undated (Box 14, Folder 61)
  - Unbearables -- "the Unbearables" by Donna Romanazzi, Endangered Species magazine, vol. 2, #1 p. 38, undated (Box 14, Folder 62)
  - Unbearables review -- Unsigned review, The Review of Contemporary Fiction, Spring 1996, p. 169 (Box 14, Folder 63)
  - Unbearables interview -- by Janice Eidus. Cups magazine. #75, p. 32, undated (Box 14, Folder 64)
  - Vitale, Alfred -- "Joe Maynard's Beet Benefit At Biblio's NYC, U-Direct magazine, Issue 2/3 p. 30, undated (Box 14, Folder 65)
  - Wilson, Blair -- "A Pentecostal Neighbor", art by Blair Wilson, Fuel, magazine, #14, n.d, undated (Box 14, Folder 66)
  - Wojnarowicz, David -- 2 works. riverrun magazine, #77, 1977. pp. 21, 57 (Box 14, Folder 67)
  - Wortsman, Peter -- "Confessions of a Tabloid Junky" Cups magazine, #75, p. 10, undated (Box 14, Folder 68)
  - Wortsman, Peter -- "Dear Reginald." A Magazine of Paragraphs, Winter 1991, Vol. 3, # 3, p. 3 (Box 14, Folder 69)
  - Zummer, Thomas -- Cover art, Disclosure magazine, #7, Spring 1985 (Box 14, Folder 70)
  - Zummer, Thomas -- Drawings, Discourse magazine, #11.2 Spring/Summer 1989, pp. 1, 87 - 97, and throughout (Box 14, Folder 71)
- Oversize - Series II: Manuscripts
  - Sparrow Manuscript Envelope, undated (Box 32, Folder 1)
- Oversize - Series III: The Unbearables
  - Bart Plantenga Boards from Brooklyn Bridge Reading, undated (Box 32, Folder 2)
  - The Unbearables Time Capsule. Do not open until 1999 (Box 32, Folder 3)
- Oversize - Series IV: Subject Files
  - Subseries A: Writers and Artists
    - McGonigle, Thomas, undated (Box 32, Folder 4)
    - Cardin, Jorga, undated (Box 32, Folder 5)
  - Subseries B: General Subjects
    - Spiegelman, Art, undated (Box 32, Folder 6)
    - Wojnarowicz, David, undated (Box 32, Folder 7)
    - Misc. subjects, undated (Box 32, Folder 8)
- Oversize - Series V: Photographs
  - Shalom Newman, "Hole Heart", undated (Box 32, Folder 9)
  - Village Voice publicity photo of the Unbearables in Thompkins Square Park, undated (Box 32, Folder 10)
  - Photo of St. Mark's Bookshop, undated (Box 32, Folder 11)
- Oversize - Series VIII: Original Art
  - Blagg, Max, original art, undated (Box 32, Folder 12)
  - Stettner, Irving, undated (Box 32, Folder 13)
- Oversize - Series X: Low Tech Press
  - Sirowitz, Hal. Production folder for Girlie Pictures, undated (Box 32, Folder 14)
  - Blagg, Max. Production folder for Monkey, undated (Box 32, Folder 15)
  - Zummer, Thomas. Production folder for Make Love Not War. Collaboration with Ron Kolm, undated (Box 32, Folder 16)
- Oversize - Series XI: Posters
  - Spiegelman, Art (Box 32, Folder 17)
- Oversize - Series XII: Catalogs
  - Brown, Ken. Mickey Mao, undated (Box 32, Folder 18)
- Oversize - Series XIII: Calendars
  This series contains Ron Kolm's calendars in which he recorded important readings and other downtown events.
  Materials are arranged chronologically.
  - 2 Calendars: 1980 & 1981 (Box 33, Folder 1)
  - 2 Calendars, 1982 & 1983 (Box 33, Folder 2)
  - 2 Calendars: 1984 & 1985 (Box 33, Folder 3)
  - 2 Calendars: 1986 (by Glen Baxter), 1987, 1986, 1987 (Box 33, Folder 4)
  - 2 Calendars: 1988 & 1989 (Box 33, Folder 5)
  - 2 Calendars: 1990 (by Glen Baxter), 1991, 1990, 1991 (Box 33, Folder 6)
  - 2 Calendars: 1992 & 1993 (Box 33, Folder 7)
  - 2 Calendars: 1994 & 1995 (Box 33, Folder 8)
  - 1 Calendar: 1996 (Box 33, Folder 9)
- Accretions 1995-1999 - Series I: Correspondence
  - Anthony, Bill, undated (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Basinski, Michael, undated (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Belle, Jennifer, undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Blagg, Max, undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Blondez, Phillipe, undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - Blowdryer, Jennifer, undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Bowery, Zagreus, undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Brown, Ken, undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Czyz, Vince, undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - deGioia, Nicole Rae, undated (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Dijkstra, Sandra, undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Duhamel, Denise, undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Eiben, Theresa, undated (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Eidus, Janice, undated (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Elie, Paul, undated (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Freels, Brandon, undated (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Freeman, Dan, undated (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Friedman, Ed, undated (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Giles, Fiona, undated (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Graham, James, undated (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Hata, Takashi, undated (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Herman, Corie, undated (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Holman, Robert, undated (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Hoover, Russell, undated (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Jurechka, Gary, undated (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Kaz, undated (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Knipfel, Jim, undated (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Kostelanetz, Richard, undated (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Leary, Mary, undated (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Lifshin, Lyn, undated (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Martin, John, undated (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Maurer, Susan, undated (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Mesmer, Sharon, undated (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Milazzo, Richard, undated (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Mutter, William, undated (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Nufer, Doug, undated (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Ochiishi, undated (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Odefey, Chad, undated (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Ortleb, Chuck, undated (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Padua, Jose, undated (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Passaro, Vince, undated (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Peabody, Richard, undated (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Phillips, Claire, undated (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Pintonelli, Deborah, undated (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Plantenga, Bart, undated (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Porton, Richard, undated (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Potts, Sam, undated (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Preston, Jane, undated (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Rappaport, Jill S., undated (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Ratner, Rochelle, undated (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Rinaldi, Karen, undated (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - Roberts, Chuck, undated (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Russell, Stefene, undated (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Rutkowski, Thad, undated (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Sandlin, David, undated (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Seigel, Judy, undated (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Shadoian, Jack, undated (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Shalom (Shalom Newman), undated (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Shine, Lori, undated (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - Simon, Dan, undated (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Sirowitz, Hal, undated (Box 15, Folder 61)
  - Sparrow (Michael Garelick), undated (Box 15, Folder 62)
  - Strausbaugh, John, undated (Box 15, Folder 63)
  - Topp, Mike, undated (Box 15, Folder 64)
  - Vitale, Alfred, undated (Box 15, Folder 65)
  - Weber, Bruce, undated (Box 15, Folder 66)
  - Witz, Robert, undated (Box 15, Folder 67)
  - Miscellaneous Correspondence, undated (Box 15, Folder 68)
- Accretions 1995-1999 - Series II: Manuscripts
  - Blagg, Max -Bohemian Veneer (from Paper), Nos. 3, 4, 11, 13, 14, 15, 16, undated (Box 15, Folder 69)
  - Blagg, Max-Pink Instrument, undated (Box 15, Folder 70)
  - Carter, Michael-Remances, undated (Box 15, Folder 71)
  - Carter, Michael-Review of C. Watson's Empire of the Birds, undated (Box 15, Folder 72)
  - Cherches, Peter-The Ideal Arrangement, undated (Box 15, Folder 73)
  - Cologne, Rank-The Bust, undated (Box 15, Folder 74)
  - Feast, Jim-False, undated (Box 15, Folder 75)
  - Feast, Jim-Kostelanetz and McLuhan, undated (Box 15, Folder 76)
  - Feast, Jim-Proposal for Seminar on Beyond Bookchin, undated (Box 15, Folder 77)
  - Feast, Jim-Reviews of C. Watson's Empire of the Birds and M. Carter's Broken Noses and Metempsychoses, undated (Box 15, Folder 78)
  - Finberg, Bonny-Freakshow, undated (Box 15, Folder 79)
  - Finberg, Bonny-It's Not His Face, undated (Box 15, Folder 80)
  - Finberg, Bonny-The Road, undated (Box 15, Folder 81)
  - Finberg, Bonny-Stalker w/ als to RK, undated (Box 15, Folder 82)
  - Finberg, Bonny-Madeleine Vlost, or Legs, or When All Else Fails, undated (Box 15, Folder 83)
  - Hardin, Rob-Sopping Up the Brood with a Dead Worm Ringing, undated (Box 15, Folder 84)
  - Huberman, David-Burnt Penises, undated (Box 15, Folder 85)
  - Huberman, David-The Most Beautiful Girl in the World, undated (Box 15, Folder 86)
  - Koan, Nancy-Truth, undated (Box 15, Folder 87)
  - Kolm, Ron-review of M. Shimada's The Dream Messenger for American Book Jam, undated (Box 15, Folder 88)
  - Kolm, Ron-Suburban Ambush, undated (Box 15, Folder 89)
  - Kolm, Ron-Factory Still Life, undated (Box 15, Folder 90)
  - Kolm, Ron-Coldest Day of the Year, undated (Box 15, Folder 91)
  - Kolm, Ron-Divine Comedy, undated (Box 15, Folder 92)
  - Kolm, Ron-Another You, undated (Box 15, Folder 93)
  - Kolm, Ron-I Am You As You Are Me, undated (Box 15, Folder 94)
  - Kolm, Ron-Open Road, undated (Box 15, Folder 95)
  - Kolm, Ron-Open File, undated (Box 15, Folder 96)
  - Kolm, Ron-The TAO of COLA, undated (Box 15, Folder 97)
  - LaBombarda, Michael-From A Gazebo, undated (Box 15, Folder 98)
  - LaBombarda, Michael-A Man Talks to His Dead Wife, undated (Box 15, Folder 99)